Agunbiade Aishat

Summary

A Web Developer specializing in front end development. Experienced with different stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects and passion for responsive website design using frontend technologies. I am intrested in joining a team where i can continue my personal growth while working to deliver accessible and efficient user-focused products.

Skill Highlights

LANGUAGES

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- SQL

FRAMEWORKS

- ReactJS
- NextJS
- Tailwind
- Bootstrap

TOOLS

- GIT & GITHUB
- FIREBASE

Experience

Web Developer Intern- 01/2022 to 06/2022

Amanda-ai technologies, Ikeja.

- Collaborated with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences. Developed project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Worked with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.
- Debugged and carried out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.

Software Developer intern- 05/2022 to 08/2022

Side-hustle internship

- Utilized HTML5/CSS3 and JavaScript to build responsive, semantic websites using efficient and clean codes.
- Collaborated with small teams to develop frontend applications.

Research Assistant- 03/2021 to 03/2022

Strategic Business TechSpace

- Utilized HTML5/CSS3 and JavaScript to build responsive, semantic websites using efficient and clean codes
- Collaborated with small teams to develop frontend applications.

Favorite Personal Projects

Portfolio website: This is my personal website which contains all my favorite websites.

Link: https://yeeshadev-portfolio.vercel.app/ code: https://github.com/YeeshaDev/portfolio

Education & Certifications

- University of Lagos | Lagos, Nigeria Bachelors of Science in Bsc. Ecotoxicology Expected in 2024.
- FreeCampCode JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Jan 2023.
- Alx Software Engineering 04/2022 to 04/2023.